Guide to the Stanford University, Office of the Vice Provost for Teaching & Learning, records SC1293
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of the Vice Provost for Teaching & Learning, records
1972-2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SC1293
21 Linear Feet (14 cartons)
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Administrative transfer, 2016.
Scope and Contents
Administrative records and audiovisual materials from the Stanford University Office of the Vice Provost for Teaching & Learning.
Stanford University -- Administration.; Universities and colleges -- Administration.
- Records, Accession ARCH_2016_122
  - Administrative records
    - Posters, introductory handbooks, and pamphlets from lectures by award winning professors, 1998-2008 (Box 1)
    - Award-winning teachers, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Publicity Award-winning teachers series, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Press coverage (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Press coverage (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Award-winning teachers, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Award-winning teaching - Fall, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Award-winning teachers, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - AWTT Tapes + Project (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Release letters returned to CTL (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - AWToT Videotape Marketing project (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Award-winning teachers, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Award-winning teachers, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Teaching Award Winners (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Award-winning teachers (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - CTL/PFR slide library (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Report of the Commission on Graduate Education, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Engendering the Curriculum, 1996 Sep 18 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Celebration of teaching "1st annual", 2005 Jun (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Celebration of teaching (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Historical miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Historical: learning assistance center continued (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - CTL teaching tips (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - publicity, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - clippings file, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - annual report, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - annual report, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - annual report, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - CTL history/background (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Historical: CTL brochures (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - annual report, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - annual report, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - annual report, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - publicity, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - CTL staff retreat, 1993 Jun 19 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - publicity, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - publicity, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - publicity, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - publicity, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - teaching resource center, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - grading + evaluating collaborative learning (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Survey development/ John Nash (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folders 3-10)
    - jigsaw (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - teaching and leadership (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - handout teaching academically diverse students (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - handout integrating reading materials and guest speakers (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - handout leading discussions (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - handout: course design worksheet (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Handout: small groups in large classes (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folders 18-23)
    - Handbook for course asssistants, 2009 Sep (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folders 25-27)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Report of the Commission, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Clarity of Explanations in Natural Sciences and Engineering Courses (Box 7)
    - Effective Lecturing: classroom environment (Box 7)
    - Effective Lecturing: classroom environment (Box 7)
    - Effective lecturing: clarity in teaching - simplifying (Box 7)
    - Effective lecturing: clarity in teaching - adapting to students (Box 7)
    - Department of Chemistry TA training manual, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - departmental TA training manual, 1996 May 17 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Faculty and TA conference on TA training, 1995 May 5 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - departmental TA training manual (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Department of Chemistry TA training program, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - departmental TA training manual (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - preparing graduate students to teach (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - course design (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Archived Masters, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Archived Masters (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Masters handouts (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - CTL Masters teaching handouts - old (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - unlabeled (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Improving University Teaching, 1980 Jul 9-12 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - the Study of Undergraduate Education at Stanford University, 2012 Jan 26 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Fisher rethinking the foreign TA problem (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Self Coaching (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - unlabeled (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Effective learning pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - informational handouts (Box 10)
    - Inspired teaching, engaged learning (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - ASSU teaching award (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Bass award (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - the Arthur L. Bloomfield Award (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Alan V. Cox medal (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Lloyd W. Dinkelspiel Award (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Earth Sciences excellence in teaching (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Franklin G. Ebaugh Jr. Award (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - school of education teaching award (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Walter J. Gores award (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Laurance and Naomi Carpenter Hoagland prize (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - School of H S dean's award (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - John Bingham Hurlbut Award (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Kaiser Foundation: excellence in clinical teaching (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Kaiser family found.: contributions to medical ed (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - kaiser award: excellence in preclinical testing (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - the Lawrence H. Mathers award (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - mba distinguished teaching award (gsb) (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - medical school dean's award for teaching (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - school of med award for graduate teaching (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - phi beta kappa teaching award (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - ph.d distinguished service award (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Lillian and Thomas B. Rhodes award (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - sloan distinguished teaching award (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - St. Clair Drake award (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - tau beta pi teaching award (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - 35th anniversary event checklist/timeline (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - invitation exception and addition (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - invitation- preparation (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - invitation additions (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - first invitation (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - invitation - double check (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - poster/advertising (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Caterer/flowers (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - photographer (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - speaker (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - facility (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - AWTT poster display (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Name tag and ribbons (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - day of documents (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - 35th anniversary materials - archive (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - expenses reconsiled (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - 35th expenses (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - second invitation (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - expense review (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - CTA Stanford report, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - CTA donors, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - CTA Stanford report, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - CTA Stanford report, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - CTA Stanford report, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - CTA Stanford report, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - CTA faculty club planning, 2009 Jun 13 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - CTA, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - CTA nominations, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - CTA timelines, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - CTA rsvp's, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - CTA Stanford report, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - CTA suggested remarks, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - CTA awardee follow-up SU-21 and rsvp, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - CTA name tags, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - CTA nomination follow-up, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - name tag calligraphy pen (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - CTA H S letter to chairs and program directors (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - CTA Dean's letter to chairs, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - CTA nomination form, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - CTA luncheon seating, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - CTA mail certificate and check, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - CTA faculty club, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - CTA database, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - CTA dean correspondence, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - CTA dean's letter awardees hard copy, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - CTA donor photos, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - CTA events and services, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - CTA chair memo certificate signature needed, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - CTA certificate printing, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - CTA certificate pickup meeting, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - CTA event signs, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - CTA donors, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - CTA engineering, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - CTA deans letter awardee email, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - CTA chair rsvps, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - CTA earth sciences, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - CTA bios and pronounciations, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - CTA calligraphy, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - CTA checks, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - cta deans calendar, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - CTA chair letter, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - CTA certificate, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - CTA check tax memo, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - CTA certificates, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - CTA day of, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - CTA stanford faculty club planning, 2010 Jun 12 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - cta dean's letter awardees, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - cta awardee lists/labels, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - awardees list, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - CTA background, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - TA Oversight Committee (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Teaching week, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - David Haliburton Workshop, 1994 May 19 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Western culture teaching workshop, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Richard Light Workshops, 1994 Apr 14-15 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Lecture series on University Teaching spring quarter, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Piper, David Warren - TA and Faculty workshops, 1994 Jan 18-19 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Faculty activities list, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Winter lecture series, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Award winning teachers on teaching lecture series, 1995-1996 Spring (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Award Winning teachers lecture series, 1995-1996 Autumn (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Lecture series on Teaching, 1993 Spring (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Meeting with pedagogy instructors at the faculty club, 1993 May 18 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Seminar on Technology, 1993 Apr 16-May 14 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - teaching and technology meeting with faculty, 1993 Jun 4 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Cox/Bligh lecture and discussion/dinner, 1995 Apr 21-22 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Lecture series, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Lecture series, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Foreign language workshop, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Talks on teaching lecture series, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Invitations to TA lectures (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - TA talks lecture series, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Effective lecturing: resources and tips (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - teaching excellence, 1995 Nov 14 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Guidelines for effective teaching (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Preparing for an academic job talk (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Effective teachers master (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Preparing for your first teaching assignment (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Documenting your teaching: creating a teaching portfolio (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Master- technology support for new faculty (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Planning Pedagogy courses important themes (Master) (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Videotaping student small group evaluations (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Video evaluation feedback form (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Videotape consent form (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - mini TA orientation, 1997-1998 Spring (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - English for foreign students info (linguistics) (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Case writing info (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Boyer commission report on educating undergraduates (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - CTL classes (flyer) (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - toward greater excellence in teaching final report C-AAA sub-committee (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - practical implications of cognitive theories, Marilla Svinicki (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - recommendation for appointment and other teaching staff (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Evaluation of oral presentation (precept program) (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - evaluation of oral presentation (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - "engendering the curriculum: textual and pedagogic strategies" for workshop (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Halliburton presentation (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - CTL annual calendar (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - CTL mission statement (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Chronical of higher education routing slip (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - travel rates at selected hotels, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - leading great discussions resources and tips (Masters) (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - "preparing for an academic job talk" Michele Marincovich (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Liaison packet (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Effective lecturing resources and tips (Masters) (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Oral Communication program student handout (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Oral Communication Masters (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Course design resources (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Successful use of teaching portfolios (handout) (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Speaking of teaching order form (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - teaching at Stanford (order form) (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - videotaping feedback form (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - TA information (for processing honorarium) (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Consultant/Liaison info form (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Letter from Liaison to facutly (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Liaison responsibilities (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Bing grants (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - CTL grants (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - unlabeled (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - report: teaching improvement at Stanford, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Centennial TA prog, 2005-2007 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Centennial TA prog, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Centennial TA prog, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Centennial TA prog, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Centennial TA prog, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Centennial TA awards, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Centennial TA Awards and Grants, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Centennial TA Awards and Grants, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - CTA Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - CTA nominations and grants, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - CTA grant proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Centennial TA nominations, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Centennial TA nominations, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Centennial TA grant proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Centennial TA nominations, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - CTA awards and grants, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - CTA grant reports, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Centennial TA grant applications, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - CTA grant reports, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Cenntenial TA proposals, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Centennial TA fundraising (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - centennial TA publicity (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - centennial TA program misc. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - centennial TA budget (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Centennial TA dinner/lunch (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Centennial TA letters and forms (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - TAOC, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - TAOC, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - unlabeled, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - TAOC, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - TAOC, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - TAOC, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - various TAOC, 1989-1996 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - TAOC, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - unlabeled (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - TA Oversight Committee, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - TA Oversight Committee, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - TAOC, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - TA Oversight Committee, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - TAOC data for H + S (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - TA Oversight Committee data on departments (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - TAOC report, 2004 Jan (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Audiovisual materials
    - Jennifer Schwartz, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - 6 TA presentations pedagogy course, 2014 Jun 9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - Greg Walton, Wise Decisions, 2013 Feb 22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - Tech- Kevin K., 2006 Sep 22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - Tech- Kevin K., 2006 Sep 22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - CT+L, 2006 Sep 22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - Phys-Astro Phys disc #2, 2011 Sep 29; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - MinT Training Day One Disc 2, 2011 Sep 29; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - CT+L disc 1, 2011 Sep 29; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - MinT Training Day 1 Disc 1, 2011 Sep 29; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - CT+L disc 1, 2011 Sep 30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - Mint Training day 2 disc 1, 2011 Sep 30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - Mint Training Day 2, Disc 2, 2011 Sep 30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - Mint Training Day 2, Disc 2, 2011 Sep 30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 3)
    - Stacey Bent CT+L AWTT, 2009 May 14; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - TA Orientation tape #1, 2010 Sep 17; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Prof. U. Inan, 2009 Apr 30; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Prof. Simon, 2009 Apr 9; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - David Beach AWTT, 2008 Nov 20; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Prof. Eric Mazur, 2008 Oct 30; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Real world Physics Eric Mazur, 2008 Oct 30; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Paula Moya, 2008 May 1; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT James Gross, 2008 Apr 24; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Prof. Oi, 2008 Mar 6; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Russell Berman, 2008 Feb 14; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Larry Diamond, 2007 Oct 31; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Debra Satz, 2007 Oct 11; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Cliff Nass, 2007 May 3; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Tom Byers, 2007 Feb 22; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Don Barn, 2007 Feb 1; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Chris Edwards, 2006 Nov 30; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Rob Dunbar AWTT, 2006 May 18; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Wanda Corn, 2006 May 4; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Landy/Anderson AWTT, 2006 Feb 23; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Gunther Walther, 2006 Jan 26; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Lanier Anderson, 2005 May 26; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Mark Applebaum, 2005 May 12; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Colt Blacker, 2005 Feb 10; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Deb Gordon AWTT Hartley Conf, 2005 Jan 20; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Eric Roberts, 2004 Nov 18; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Bob Gregg AWTT, 2004 Nov 11; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT John Rick, 2004 Feb 12; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Robert Gray, 2004 Jan 22; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Robert Gray, 2004 Jan 22; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Seth Lever AWTT, 2003 Nov 20; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Roger Neil AWTT, 2003 Nov 13; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Paul Wender, 2003 May 15; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Paul Wender, 2003 May 15; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Laura Carstensen, 2003 Feb 27; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Jane Sheehan, 2003 Feb 13; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Joel Beinin 2, 2003 Jan 30; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Joel Beinin 1, 2003 Jan 30; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Eric Kool 2, 2002 May 16; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Eric Kool 1, 2002 May 16; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT David Freyburg, 2002 Apr 25; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Hans Ulrich Gumbrecht, 2002 Jan 31; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Hans Ulrich Gumbrecht, 2002 Jan 31; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Patricia Burchet, 2002 Jan 24; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT David Abernethy, 2001 Oct 25; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Keith Loague, 2001 Apr 19; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Al + Barbara Gelpi, 2001 Jan 31; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Timothy Lenoir, 2000 Dec 9; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Kristine Samuelson, 2001 Nov 29; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Jeff Koseff, 2000 May 4; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Mary Barth, 2000 Apr 13; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Peter Sells, 2000 Feb 24; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Franklin On, 2000 Feb 10; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Richard Zare, 2000 Feb 3; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Franklin Orr, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Brad Gregory, 1999 May 13; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - AWTT Robert Weisberg, 1999 Apr 29; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Mary Louise Roberts, 1999 Apr 22; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Ramon Saldivar, 1999 Feb 29; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)